all right
uh i'm gonna wait for you guys to get
on make sure you can hear me all right
i think yeah my microphone looks like
it's working so
um hello everyone
uh i'm just getting on to make
a quick announcement uh
all right very good very good very good
okay so listen guys
tomorrow october 12th that is monday
and tuesday october 13th i'm gonna be
hosting a
revelation lockdown all right
this is going to be a class on the
entire book of revelation
um we're going to be going
hills the seven churches the seven
trumpets the seven plagues
we're going to be looking at how the
sanctuary helps us to better understand
the book of revelation
we're going to be looking at the the
overview of the book of revelation and
how it fits
in with the new testament we're going to
see some amazing
things if you've ever wanted to
understand this book um
i want to encourage you to join this
class okay i'm going to put the link
in the description of this video so that
you can click on that link and it'll
take you over to where you can sign up
for the class
it's going to be at 1 pm that's 1 p.m
pacific standard time
on monday that is tomorrow and tuesday
so this is a two-day course
and i want you to know that um even if
you if you're busy at that time for
those who sign up for this class
uh it will be recorded all right you
will have access to it
uh so again it's 1 p.m pacific standard
time
um will
understand the book of revelation in a
way that is going to be very
easy it's going to be simplified that's
why i'm calling it revelation
juiced because we're going to juice down
the entire book
and if there was ever a time to
understand the book of revelation
that time is now that time is now
so once again guys i just want to
encourage you to sign up for the class
you will not regret it um i will put the
link
in in the uh in the description and
i hope to see you monday that is
tomorrow
and tuesday all right i'll bless you
and i will see you soon